<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoTwoNineZero</string>
    <string name="by_clicking">By clicking REGISTER you agree to our Terms &amp; Conditions</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dash_board_drawer">DashBoardDrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="aboutus">About Us</string>
    <string name="contactus">Contact</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="convienent">convienent</string>
    <string name="internet_required">Internet Required</string>
    <string name="mybusiness_no_text">You dont have any business at this moment. Go to add new business for filing the tax</string>
    <string name="myfleet_no_text">You dont have any fleet at this moment.</string>
    <string name="aboutus_firstpara">E-filing Form 2290 just got easier and more affordable with Simple truck tax. Our user-friendly system allows you to file your return in minutes and makes paying your tax bill a breeze \n \n &#160; &#160; &#160; &#160; &#160; When we designed our product, SimpleTruckTax, we had only one goal in mind - making sure that YOU, the American Truckers, don\'t have to break the bank to keep your trucks running on the road. We looked at several online 2290 products on the market and were saddened to see that NONE of them were easy to use, especially for the fortune that they were charging. The reality was that good hard working American Truckers like you were spending upwards of $100 and wasting hours doing something that nobody likes doing - TAXES! That is when we decided to put our minds to work and figure out how we can make filing your truck taxes not only quick and easy but also affordable</string>
    <string name="home_no_text">You dont have any return status at this moment.\nGo to business navigation and add a new business</string>
    <string name="addbusiness_signauth">Would you like to authorize a person to discuss your tax returns with the IRS ? If yes the designee name and the phone number are mandatory</string>
    <string name="consent_to_disclosure">I hereby give consent to the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) disclosing information about my payment of the Heavy Highway Vehicle Use Tax (HVUT) for the tax period listed above to the federal Department of Transportation (DOT), U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP), and to state Departments of Motor Vehicles (DMV). The information disclosed to the DOT, CBP, and state DMVs will be my Vehicle Identification Number (VIN) and verification that I have paid the HVUT. The IRS may disclose the information to the DOT, CBP, and to the DMVs of the 50 states and the District of Columbia who have other taxing, registration, or information collecting authority. I agree that the American Association of Motor Vehicle Administrators (AAMVA), a third-party nonprofit organization, may be used as an intermediary to transmit my VIN and payment information from the IRS to the state DMVs. \n \n I understand that the information to be disclosed is generally confidential under the laws applicable to the IRS and that the agency receiving the HVUT information is not bound by these laws and may use the information for any purpose as permitted by other federal laws and/or state law. To be effective, this consent must be received to the IRS within 120 days of the date of filing with the IRS. \n \n If signed by a corporate officer or party other than the Taxpayer, I certify that I have the authority to execute this consent to disclosure of tax information. The personal identification Number will be used only if the return is electronically transmitted to the IRS</string>


</resources>